Memories that persist through 30 million years...
In the never-stopping, never-reversing,
never-changing flux,
feelings are memories that cross time.
Feelings are memories that have reached the gate of fate.
A dream?
Karamatta ito ga kishimi atte
The intertwined threads compete
mujun teiku wo uwagaki suru
Overwriting any contradictory takes
Rifujin wa itsuka konsen shite
Irrationality is going haywire
ai mo mirai sae mo koroshite yuku
Putting our love and our future to death
Bamen goto ni ukande kuru
The scenes we shared come to mind
kizuna mitaina sono zenbu ga
All of them like bonds between us
Mabushii hodo kagayai teru
They shine in a blinding light
bajji ni shirushita kakegae nai mono
Inscribed on the irreplaceable badge
I believe it
Fly away sekai wa owari ga hajimaru
Fly away as the world begins to end
Futsugouna asu wo nomikonde ku
The unwanted tomorrow will be consumed
Loneliness kodoku no deja vu ni toraware
Loneliness, imprisoned in the déjà vu of solitude
Kaisen wa yagate tachikira reta
The circuit is finally severed
Ichiga kiete zeroni naru ishiki no surikae
"1" disappears and becomes "0" as a consciousness is usurped
Anata no me wa ima nani wo utsushi teru no?
What do those eyes of yours reflect now?
Hey, you there.
Can you see us? Why don't you answer us?
I'm talking to you, with the dumb expression!
Tutturu~
I'm Mayushii!
Hey, Lab Member No. 003, Supah Hakah.
Say something.
It's "Hacker," not "Hakah," duh!
He never says anything.
But there has been a development.
Thanks to a year of persistent effort,
due to our inquisitive minds, he produced offspring!
So cute!
Normalfags should just get out.
It's only logical to assume that somewhere within this software lies
the secret code to reconstructing this world's ruling structure!
I'll uncover it at any cost! On my name, Hououin Kyouma!
Daru, do you want some barley tea?
Yes, please.
Mayushii, when you serve tea you should say, "Here's your tea."
"Here's your tea?"
Yeah. "I'll leave your tea here," is good too.
And you, Okarin?
Do you think I could drink the beverage of commoners?
I only consume the intellectual drink of the chosen ones!
Dr Pepper, right?
Mayuri.
Switch on Future Gadget No.10 Cool Visitor!
But it doesn't cool the air very well...
Don't you worry.
It's been half a day since we suspended continuous operation.
It's got plenty of cool air inside.
Really?
So? Feels good, right?
It doesn't feel any different from a normal fan.
Actually, the heat released by the motor is stronger than the cold air.
The tea doesn't feel that cold anymore, either...
Be silent! A new discovery is just around the corner and—
Just shutting off like that is the worst possible thing that could happen to my data!
You—!
If I lose all of my game character data, I'll kill you, and then commit suicide!
Tears?
Okabe!
Oh, no!
You bastard! Get down here!
If you need something, then you should come upstairs, Mr. Braun!
Shut it! I'll add 5,000 yen to your rent!
I'll be right there!
Nae!
Mayuri!
Braun Tube Studio
Future Gadget Lab
Summer 2010.
One year has passed since I reached
the Steins Gate world line.
Mayuri is alive. Kurisu wasn't killed
and neither the time machine nor D-mail exist in this world.
Time proceeds only forward, never backward,
the future doesn't change,
and there isn't a single other world line in existence...
Mayuri—
Okarin?
What's wrong?
Nothing...
Listen, Okarin.
Are you sure?
Yes, the survival of my Future Gadget Lab depends on
this mission I have to clear.
The important mission Mr. Braun entrusted to me is—
Oh. Well, Ruka is waiting for me, so see you later.
Welcome back. Are you here on your summer holiday?
Not your business.
Isn't she here yet?
It landed a while ago. She shouldn't be long...
Kurisu!
Welcome back!
Mayuri! You came all the way here to pick me up?
Yep. I couldn't wait!
Long time no see.
Indeed... Urushibara, right?
Yes.
But he's a guy.
You'll stop by the lab, right?
Y-Yes... it's still early, so...
The station has changed a lot too.
Yep, there's a new GunBam Cafe, and an idol bar...
Even Radio Kaikan's been rebuilt.
A lot's changed in a year, I guess. What about the lab?
No particular change there, I guess...
Oh, but... Daru made a friend!
A girl!
You're kidding!
She's a cosplayer, Amane...Yuki?
Yes. I heard they met online.
She's very pretty.
Pret... ty?
Here she is.
Is... Hashida's family rich or something?
Don't think so...
Then he must have won the lottery.
I didn't hear about anything like that either...
Then...
It's Daru!
Daru!
Mayu—! It's Miss Makise?! Long time—
If you're trying to trick her, come clean!
What are you talking about?
Trick? Daru?
I don't think that's the case...
You said you exchanged photos the other day, right?
What kind of photo did you send?
Well...
Photoshop, huh.
Of course. No girl would go near such a pervert otherwise.
That's mean! Don't judge!
But she said her type is bear-like guys, didn't she?
Y-Yeah...
Don't you dare assume that a woman saying
"Bear-like guys are my type" means "I'm into fat guys!"
What's that? You're scary!
Messy as always.
Kurisu.
Here's your tea.
Thx!
You still talk like an @channel user...
Shut up!
But Okarin sure is late.
He said that after the errand for Mr. Braun,
he'd go to Ameyoko to buy something.
But Miss Makise took the trouble to come over...
It-It's no big deal!
Kurisu, are you all right?
I'm very all right, Mayuri.
Actually, I'm almost relieved he's not here!
Don't need to waste any energy...
Template: Tsundere Queen.
I'm neither tsun nor dere!
Darn that Mr. Braun!
He chose a faraway store on purpose!
It's me. Yes...
Looks like a new agent from the Organization.
What?! An emergency request?
I got it. If that's Steins;Gate's choice...
"El Psy Kongroo."
Still as annoying as usual.
Sorry.
Long time no see, assistant.
I mean, Cristina.
No, experiment-loving perverted girl.
"Pervert" for short!
There's a limit to rudeness!
Hah! That reaction... It seems you are the real Cristina.
Cristina!
There's no "tina"!
But, Cristina!
The Future Gadget Lab is a secret state organization.
It's only natural that to get in, you need proper authorization.
Remember that.
I'm a lab member. I have the right to come and go as I please!
You haven't shown up for a year
and dare make such a wild claim?
And you call yourself my assistant?!
It feels like being back in the old lab.
I said I'm not your assistant nor am I Cristina!
Yes, Mayushii is very happy.
By the way, experiment-loving perverted genius girl?
No!
Why did you come to Japan, pervert girl?
To apologize for not showing up at the lab?
Why should I apologize?!
There's a conference here in Japan, so I just dropped by!
And I wanted to see Mayuri too.
Here's a souvenir.
Really?! Thank you!
It's a sewing set I found in the US.
This is for you, Urushibara.
Thank you so much!
And for me, some uncensored American version of something...
Customs would arrest me!
There's nothing for you guys! I only came to see Mayuri and Urushibara.
I wasn't expecting anything in the least!
Now that you understand, leave this place at once!
You don't need to tell me! I was going anyway!
I need to check into the hotel.
What? You're leaving already?
I'll be in Japan for a while. I'll get in touch with you again.
Sorry for the wait, Kyouma! Nyan~!
Sorry for intruding...
Faris and Moeka! What are you two doing here?
What? Aren't we having a barbecue? Nyan~!
Kyouma just came by and said, nyan~,
that we should have a barbecue today because Ku-nyan is coming.
I... got a mail...
Okarin...
What's this? Due to the increasing activity of a solar storm,
auditory hallucinations and unlikely telecommunications are occurring?!
Don't tell me the Seven Sages of Seiryuzan have sprung into actionyan!?
That's unforgivable! I'll demand an apology!
Calm down, please!
The fact that all the lab members have been reunited here
is Steins;Gate's choice.
Mayuri! Prepare for the round table meeting!
Okay!
Rukako!
Y-Yes!
You didn't say the password.
E... El Psy... Kongree?
It's "Kongroo," Ruka.
Kurisu, you do have time, right?
Kind of...
No more tsundere!
You too, Okarin.
He can never be honest about his feelings...
Mix! Mix! Mix! Mix! Mix! Mix!
Wow! Eye-contact Mix Mix Yakisoba!
Oh, that may be a bit undercooked.
No problem.
It was undercooked...
The second was fine.
Oh! Nae, you can eat peppers?! I'm impressed!
Yeah, but my daddy can't.
It's been a year...
What... was that?
Okabe!
What's up, Cristi—
I'm just not convinced!
What are you talking about?
The time machine! It's impossible!
Theoretically—!
You're too close!
Oh! Don't tell me you're—
There should only be alcohol-free beer...
Now this is real beer!
Hey, are you listening?
W-What?
I'm talking about before!
What you told me when you came to the States!
About another world line, and that something happened to another me...
Then you took advantage of the fact that I didn't understand
and in the confusion, even did that thing...
That... thing?
W-Wait! Are you bringing that up here and now?!
What? So it's really that shameful for you?
No... that's not...
You know, that time... I was quite...
That time...
H-Hey!
Is something wrong, nyan~?
N-Nothing!
Faris' Special End of the Century Yakisoba's almost ready, nyan~!
This guy hasn't even sent me a single email since last summer!
Even after he did "that thing!"
Telling me "I love you."
Then blaming it on another word line—
Give it a break. Come here!
Let go of me!
That was dangerous—
Okabe...
W-What?
Hold me!
H-Hey...
Shave. Shave.
Hey, you! Wait!
Prickly.
What if someone comes?!
You don't want that?
What?
You don't want to be seen?
No, it's not that...
Then it's fine, right?
No... but...
Yes or no?! Which is Steins;Gate's choice?!
No... I-I mean...
You! Be clear!
W-Wait!
Here, assistant.
Cool your head a bit.
Thanks.
Good grief...
Good grief what?
Trying to pick a fight again?
I wish I could tell you.
I'm a scientist. I don't want to accept the idea of
past life encounters, destiny,
and world lines... or time machines.
I know that...
But... even though I try to deny them in theory,
something keeps bothering me...
My head gets all messed up...
T-This is...
A spoon... and fork...
You wanted them, so...
Yes, I did...
But I never told you that...
I see... It wasn't on this world line...
It feels like someone's been peeping on my thoughts...
Sorry, I'm going to rest a bit.
Okarin, there's going to be no yakisoba left for you!
Hey... Mayuri.
I told you before, right?
That I came here from a different world line?
Yes, you were with another Mayushii and another Kurisu, right?
What do you think about that story?
Why?
Well... Kurisu is...
Mayushii doesn't think Okarin's lying, so it must be true.
But that's because Mayushii can't understand difficult things...
Kurisu is really smart,
so maybe she's thinking really hard about what Okarin said.
I'll be upstairs, okay?
A time machine...
What?!
Mayuri!
Okarin,
do you know where we put the new dish cloth?
It's not on the shelf, so... maybe it's under the stove?
Here it is! Mr. New Dish Cloth!
What's wrong, Okarin?
This is...?
It's fun to eat outside, even if it's on top of the lab!
A barbecue with Faris! My heart's on fire!
Mayuri!
What?
Come this way!
Okarin?! What's wrong?!
Wake up, Kurisu!
Quick!
What's up with you?!
Hurry!
Okabe? What...
Be quiet!
Hey, you guys forgot this on the roof—
Don't move!
What the hell?! Okabe...
Kurisu! The time leap-machine, quick!
We don't have time! Quick!
Okabe, calm down! There's no such thing here!
What are you saying?! It's just over there—
This is the Steins Gate world line?
Steins?
Yes, the world line you told me
you finally reached.
Is that right? I'm sorry...
What the hell was that?
What was that just now?
A dream? A delusion?
No, it was real without a doubt.
I was in another world line.
But I'm not using a D-mail or the time machine...
No, be rational! That can't be possible!
It's a delusion, a daydream.
The memories of another world line are just making it feel like reality—
What a nice view!
Human beings are creatures who need time to unwind once in a while.
I have more fun working on the time leap machine...
It's so hot! Why is this happening to me?
You're too fat, Daru. You should exercise more.
What is this place?
You're so sloppy!
You won't survive if you continue like that.
Suzuha...
I will never forgive you.
You drove my daddy to his death.
Stop!
They're getting... longer?
Okarin.
Mayuri...
Are you okay?
Yes, no need to worry.
I'm sorry about earlier. My right arm
went berserk against my will!
That's okay. I was just a little scared.
Oh, you're sweating a lot!
Sorry...
No problem. This is all Mayushii can do.
Lately, Mayushii's been having a recurring dream
where Okarin comes and saves Mayushii over and over again...
It's Mayushii's fault you always look so sad...
Mayuri.
It's just a dream.
Okarin...
It's nothing but a dream.
You're right.
Let's go home.
Okay.
You hugged me like this that time too.
Thank you, Okarin.
Excuse me!
No Cell Phones
Good morning, Faris.
Good mornyan!
How is it?
Not good, Manager.
Not good?
With this month's energy bill alone, we're already 28,568 yen in the red.
Should I raise the rent for real?
I came all the way to Japan.
I'd like to relax in a hot bath at least once.
Who is it?
The maid?
Didn't I put up the "Do Not Disturb" sign?
Oh? What's this?
Makise Kurisu.
I don't have time, so I'll tell you only this.
Who are you?!
Cell phone, microwave oven,
SERN.
Don't forget.
Don't forget, and you'll find a way.
As long as you continue to observe...
you will not fail...
Who are you?
Cell phone,
microwave oven, SERN?
What on earth was that?
It didn't look like they stole anything, but...
I'll move to another room. That was creepy.
What was creepy... Cristina?
N-Nothing in particular!
It's not like something scary happened to me at the hotel...
Never mind that! Why are you here?!
That's my line.
While removing the medals I amassed during my research known as "dirt,"
I was recalling my own accomplishments.
I don't wish to be disturbed!
Unfortunately, this is neither the lab nor your home!
Let me through!
It's not like I enjoy doing laundry with you.
Hey! Don't open without asking.
Take your stuff out when it's done!
Look at how ragged this lab coat's gotten.
Assistant, those are Daru's...
underpants.
Good thing I had some antiseptic on me!
Daru would be saddened if he saw the way you reacted.
It's because you always wear that worn-out coat that I got confused!
A worn-out lab coat is part of the scientific aesthetic.
There's a limit!
Look, the sleeve's torn.
Give it to me. I'll stitch it for you.
W-What?!
No... It's nothing...
It's normal to carry a sewing kit, even for me!
Y-Yeah, that's right.
This...
It's the kind of coat we use in America.
You should keep a spare.
It was made in the US. It should be perfect for your height.
Really? You bought it just for me?
No! It's just a coincidence!
I had an extra one, that's all.
And since you gave me that spoon and fork...
I'm warning you, though.
Don't complain about how I do it.
And I don't have any white thread, so...
Right...
What?
Nothing...
Is it about something that happened in another world line again?
Yes... And yet, not so.
What was that self-contradicting statement?
There's no doubt that thanks to my Reading Steiner ability,
I could observe other world lines and still retain memories of them.
And among those countless world lines that continued to converge and diverge,
I drifted
and miraculously reached the only one I really wanted to be on.
On this world line, you are sitting here with me,
and Mayuri is working part-time at MayQueen...
That's enough for me. I can't ask for more.
Okabe...
I wanted the you of this world line
to get to know more about me,
so maybe I've said more than I should.
I'm sorry.
What?
That's all I have to say.
Your hand has stopped, assistant!
I-I know! But...
I just wonder if everything you said is true...
It is only natural to doubt
the existence of world lines...
It's not that.
If countless world lines do exist,
I can hardly believe that only you retain memories of them.
That the Reading Steiner is yours alone...
Do you dislike that?
Not really, but...
For example, right now I'm here sewing your coat.
It shouldn't be possible, but I have the impression that it's happened before.
You want to say it's déjà vu, don't you?
I did too. But it happens so often when I'm with you.
Tell me, have I done this same thing in another world line?
I knew I did.
What's your point?
Déjà vu is considered to be
an anomaly caused by the overlapping of short-term memory and long-term memory.
In other words, it's a phenomenon created by a temporal discrepancy of memories.
Reading Steiner is the retention
of memories of multiple world lines generated by the alteration of the past.
Thus, both are memory anomalies created in the brain by temporal misplacement.
I actually just confirmed a different world line occurrence
based on a memory I had acknowledged as déjà vu.
You're saying that déjà vu is a form of Reading Steiner?
It may be difficult to demonstrate, but it's possible.
I plan to write a paper on it after I get back.
No matter where you go, you never change.
You experiment-loving girl!
I'll take that as a compliment.
Anyway, if anything happens, let me know.
That's—
Tutturu~
It's lunch time!
Mayushii, did you bring my lunch?
Yep.
Today's lunch is the new Juicy
Karaage Number 1 boxed lunch!
Didn't we have that yesterday?
Another invention?
Yup.
I was upgrading the Future Gadget No. 10 Cool Visitor.
Now it's perfect!
You love inventing stuff, don't you, Daru?
That's why I started the Future Gadget Lab, duh.
It's Kurisu!
What's wrong?
Where is he?
He?
That guy!
We were at the laundromat and all of a sudden, he was gone.
Like I said, who?
You know, that guy who's always here...
The founder of this lab.
Of this lab?
That would be me.
What?! What are you saying?
Oh, do you mean Ruka?
No!
Faris? Or Miss Kiryuu?
Not them! You know, that...
Right! Lab Member No. 001...
001?
001 is a vacant number.
We told you before, Kurisu.
We're keeping 001 open.
But...
Then what about this lab coat?
That's yours, Kurisu.
Mine?
You're right.
Why was I in a panic?
Mayushii was wondering what happened.
Sorry.
Have you gone nuts, Miss Makise?
I haven't!
I think that was the first moment I felt something was out of place.
Something was missing.
Something I thought existed wasn't there anymore.
It's definitely something, but...
I don't know what it is.
Something felt off, as if this world wasn't real. Like it was fake.
There was an uneasy feeling that something was manipulating my memory.
At the same time, I wondered if it was all just a delusion
and feared I was going crazy...
A restless urge to recall and the temptation
to forget everything to achieve peace of mind were clashing constantly.
A week later, just as that uncomfortable feeling was fading...
TAKING MY FORK
Shinichirou
USING MY SPOON
A clue emerged.
My fork...
Cell phone
Microwave oven
Don't forget, and you'll find a way.
Hello?
Can I ask you something real quick?
I'm currently in my Super After-Glow State. Ask away!
I didn't need to know that!
You know about SERN, right?
Gulp... Why? Were you spying on my computer?
What do you mean?
How do you know about my solo hacking job?
Hacking?! Hacking SERN?! Why?
Why?! Because... Huh, I'm not sure.
Stay at the lab. I'll be right there.
Cell phone...
SERN!
That ribbon is so cute!
Isn't it?
Wanna try it on? I have other costumes for the next ComiMa.
Cosplay?
Interested?
Of course not! I could never wear something like that in public.
Finished!
Mayushii wins!
You beat us! But we're done too.
It's complete. This is...
This is the time-leap machine! Intense...
I'm not fully convinced myself.
But by using the LHC hacked from SERN, we can compress brain signals
and send them from here to the past with this Phone Microwave.
At least theoretically, it is feasible.
Well thought!
More like "remembered."
Have you made this before, Miss Makise?
No... I have no memory of it.
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
But it's inside me, like a fragment...
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Me on 2011/8/13 AD
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Kaiba
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Hippocampus
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
Nerve Pulse Signals —> Encode to Electric Signals
Scan Memory Data (3.24T)
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
seconds
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
seconds
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
seconds
A so-called "déjà vu"?
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
seconds
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
seconds
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
seconds
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
seconds
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
seconds
Time Leap Machine
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
Send through the internet!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Bytes
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
seconds
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Generate black hole with LHC
Use energy to compress data!
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Return!
23ms
Compression!
Time Leap Machine
Return!
23ms
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Return!
23ms
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Return!
23ms
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
23ms
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
23ms
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
I don't know...
23ms
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
23ms
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
23ms
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap Machine
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
Time Leap!
Phone call
Overwrite memory
data in the brain!
Me on 2011/8/3 AD
But, for example, why did you decide to hack SERN, Hashida?
Um, well...
It kind of felt like a super-exciting thing to do.
Is that all?
Wasn't there a part of you that felt you had to do something?
Mayuri, why do you always buy Dr Pepper?
Because I always think someone will drink it...
But neither Hashida nor I particularly like the drink.
Nor do you, Mayuri.
Yet you buy Dr Pepper every day.
Do I?
Something's...
Something isn't right...
Something's missing...
Cell phone
Microwave oven
What?
I'm not sure. That's why...
No way!
Kurisu, are you going to use this?
Right. If I'm able to use this machine to go back in time,
I might seriously alter the world by changing the past.
But I can't leave this situation as it is now.
What do you wanna do?
I'll go back to the day before I went to that laundromat.
I more or less remember what I did that day.
Can you go back further than 48 hours?
Who said that the limit is 48 hours?
Oh?
Why did I think that?
I'll act according to my memory, minimizing my impact on the past.
I'll only be there
to trace the origin of this uneasy feeling.
But will it work?
I won't push it any further if it doesn't.
And I'll never use this machine again.
Neither should the two of you.
It's connected!
Are you sure about this, Miss Makise?
Hashida, please!
Okay. Let's do this!
Mix! Mix! Mix! Mix! Mix! Mix!
Wow! Eye-contact Mix Mix Yakisoba!
Oh! Nae, you can eat peppers?!
I'm impressed!
Yeah, but my daddy can't.
Nae, Mayuri,
Hashida, Faris,
the Manager, Kiryuu, and Urushibara.
Okabe!
Kurisu, what's wrong?
Is Okarin okay?
Okabe...
Why did I forget about him?
No, I didn't forget. It was like he never existed...
Now, as the founder of this lab I'll do the first toast of the night!
Let's first make sure that everyone's got a drink, nyan~!
Not ready yet? Cheers!
It's like Okabe doesn't exist...
Here.
Can Okarin eat shrimp?
Okabe!
Looks like your time leap was successful.
Who is this?
The building on the right.
In order to be able to speak to you, Makise Kurisu,
I needed you to become an observer of this world.
Observer?
By time-leaping into the past,
you were able to acknowledge the disappearance of Okabe Rintarou—
Wait! Before that, who are you?
Oh, sorry! You haven't met me yet!
My name is Amane Suzuha.
I came from the future
with the time machine built by the future you.
The time machine... I built?
Yes, it all sounds hard to believe,
but the Steins Gate world line is a great danger for Okabe Rintarou.
His memories of other world lines
are overloading his Reading Steiner
and it's becoming difficult for him to remain on this world line.
Then where is he?
He's most likely on the "R" world line.
It's only 0.000001% off from the one we're on now...
This is the sole world line that avoids both
the convergences of Shiina Mayuri's and Makise Kurisu's deaths.
That's why it's more unstable than others and fluctuates,
and there's the "R" world line just next to it.
The memories of the drifting world lines
overloading the Reading Steiner are causing
Okabe Rintarou to pick up on that fluctuation
and time-leap to the "R" world line.
...And it's as though he never existed on this one.
Is that the cause of my vertigo?
Okabe...
You were listening?
Yes, I can hardly believe it,
but if this is the word of the Part-Time Soldier, it must be true.
Part-time soldier? What's that?
No, on this world line you're neither a part-timer nor a soldier...
Okabe!
Okabe?
I'll disappear?
Yes... tomorrow morning
and then you will never have existed
in everyone's minds.
Never existed...
Powerful memories from other world lines act as triggers that cause
the Okabe Rintarou observing this world line as a reality
to sense these fluctuations and oscillate between lines himself.
Memory cannot be controlled...
That's troublesome.
No matter how much we may want to forget them,
memories we cannot forget remain, in spite of our will.
Especially for you, Okabe...
You experienced strong fear and sadness on the other world lines,
and the self-reproach you felt remains in your memory too.
Now you see the same people,
the same room, the same city, and the same words from your memories.
They'd be impossible to forget.
Memories of other world lines, which seem like dreams but aren't...
Memories that are real when they shouldn't be.
This ambiguity turns your awareness into a risk.
So you came from the future to save me?
You could say that.
The only way to save Okabe Rintarou is to go to the past with the time machine.
So...
I refuse!
Return to the future at once.
Then destroy the Time Machine right away.
It cannot be allowed to exist. Destroy it immediately!
Wait!
I was finally able to come here with the time-leap machine!
What?! Don't tell me that you... The time-leap...!
I built it with Hashida using the cell phone, the microwave oven, and...
Why did you do that?!
Time-leap machines and time machines should never be built!
Even if you can figure out how to do it,
you should never ever build one!
Okabe... you're hurting me!
Sorry...
But if I don't do something, you'll vanish.
You will never have existed...
I have no choice but to change the past—
And what if you fail?
What if it doesn't go well?
The answer is simple.
You do it again.
You keep going back to the past until you succeed.
As long as they have the means to go back in time, that's what people will do.
But it'll only increase the suffering.
A change in the past will always affect something else.
It will never change in a way that's convenient for you.
If you save someone,
you will lose someone...
Dreams you finally fulfilled won't exist anymore.
Your long-held desires will be snatched away, eradicated...
And when the change you hoped for doesn't happen,
you will have to keep facing that inescapable reality
again and again, again and again!
Do you realize the pain of continuously repeating all of that,
while bearing the responsibility for all those losses?
Do you understand the fear of losing your humanity after it wears you down?
But...
Even if you have the means, the past must not be changed.
You must not turn chance into reality.
No one knows the future.
It's because the past cannot be undone that people can accept all sorts of pain,
adversity, and cruel accidents, yet still move forward.
Then what are you going to do, Okabe?
You're going to disappear!
I... saw it...
A world where you don't exist...
A lab with only Mayuri, Hashida, and me...
Where nobody remembers you...
It was crueler than death!
Any mark or meaning of your existence will disappear!
I don't care.
Okabe...
All I wanted was for you and Mayuri to live in peace
and keep walking towards the future.
Nothing more.
It's fine as long as that comes true.
What you're saying now, the things you've accomplished,
even your name... We'll forget everything!
But Mayuri won't die, and you can keep on living too.
How long will you go on following me?
I'm not! I'm just going to the station.
But your hotel's not this way.
I've got somewhere to go.
Where?
It's my business, not yours.
I'm warning you.
What?
The moment I disappear tomorrow,
the people around you will think I never existed,
but since you came here with a time-leap,
you may still remember me.
Yes... I suppose so.
To a small degree, Reading Steiner is present in every human being.
Since you've been leaping through time,
you may experience it more than others.
What are you trying to say?
Forget.
Forget me.
Just like the others, think that I never existed.
This moment was just a dream.
Remembering something that no one else can is a painful thing.
You can't talk to anyone about it. No one will understand you.
You'll be alone.
So that's how it's been for you all this time?
Then...
Kurisu...
Then... it's no good.
You have to exist!
If that's what I did for you on another world line,
then do the same for me!
Stay by my side. Listen to what I say!
Suffering alone...
Then disappearing by yourself...
That's...
That's... That's too selfish!
There's no need to worry. Daru is my right hand.
You can rely on him in your hour of need.
Mayuri might not look it, but she's more mature than you in some respects.
During the hard times, you can cry on her shoulder. She'll always be there.
Faris and Rukako will help you too.
There's nothing to worry about.
Stupid! That's not what I'm trying to say—
You're horrible...
You do something that'll leave a deep imprint in the hippocampus
and then tell me to forget you?
You're horrible...
Sorry...
Okabe didn't contact me at all after that.
Neither by phone... nor email.
I didn't contact him, either.
I didn't know what to say to him.
I couldn't say anything...
I'm sure Okabe also felt...
Goodbye
Okabe
Stupid.
Stupid! Why...
Why?!
Now it's like I'm the stupid one!
Being told some obscure nonsense, getting pushed around...
Getting told "I love you"
and not being able to forget you...
At this rate, if this...
Okarin!
This is Dr Pepper color, isn't it?
Yes, the very embodiment of intelligence.
Requesting to see you in it, Mayushii.
Silence, Perverted Gentleman.
Okabe! Okabe!
What was that?!
There's no way I can forget you...
Because I've known you for a long, long time...
And I've loved you for a long, long time...
And I will always...
Always...
Okarin?
It's nothing... I'm fine.
Kurisu!
Okabe!
Kurisu...
Okabe, I—
Mayushii! Tissue! Tissue! Quick!
Y-Yes! Tissue! Tissue!
There! There!
Kurisu?
What's up?
Where is he?
He?
That guy... He was just there...
Like I said. Who?
You know... That guy!
The one who's always here, the founder of this lab...
Of this lab?
That's me.
Okabe... Rintarou
Yes... Okabe... Rintarou...
What's wrong, Kurisu?
Did you run into a pervert?
Hashida! Lend me your cell phone!
What? Why?
Just do it! Then hack into SERN immediately.
Wha—?!
Hurry!
It's wrong! I won't accept it!
No matter what you tell me...
That's no good, Kurisu.
Mayuri...
Mayushii doesn't really understand, but...
Mayushii thinks it'll only hurt you.
That's when I made my decision
to accept your wish.
I won't manipulate time or the past
and will accept this world you fiercely protected
Future Gadget Lab
as reality.
I will forget my memories of you
and the name Okabe Rintarou,
and I'll just keep walking towards the unknown future...
because that's what you wanted.
Oh, Daru?
You're not coming today, either?
It's too hot at the lab! And there's the Rai-Net tournament today.
Oh...
Why don't you come too, Mayushii? Do a twin battle with Faris!
But I'm not on shift today...
See you later, then.
Yeah.
Are you ready?
We will now initiate Operation Midgard!
Moeka! What's wrong?
He wants to talk to you...
The Manager...
In other words, there is also the theory that we still haven't reached
a correct neuroscientific conclusion on why
the phenomenon known as "dreaming" occurs, nor what it is needed for.
I will continue on this subject in our next lecture.
Brain
Confusion
Mystery
Brain
Confusion
Mystery
I need to decide where to go for dinner.
Well, we can't do anything about it.
Are you serious?
Mayushii tried to save her pocket money too, but it's not enough...
So you're giving up? We'll lose the lab.
Why are you so upset, Miss Makise?
I...
Lately, I've just started to feel like it's a pain to pay the rent.
Mayushii didn't realize...
I started this lab because I thought that maybe we could do something,
but in the end...
What's going to happen to Mayuri?! She won't have a place to go!
Mayushii will be okay. Mayushii has the café.
Mayuri...
Actually, Mayushii was feeling the same way.
Lately, when Mayushii comes to the lab, Mayushii gets kind of lonely...
It's like...
Something's missing...
What is?
The thing is... Mayushii doesn't know what.
I see...
See you, then.
The lab won't close right away. I'll email you, okay?
Okay...
Cheer up, Kurisu.
Thank you. I'll be fine.
I'm going, then.
Address does not exist.
The lab might be dissolved.
To: Okabe Rintarou
Address does not exist.
The lab might be dissolved.
To: Okabe Rintarou
This is reality. This is the world...
Exactly. This world line's reality.
I thought I'd at least come to say hello.
I decided to go back to the future.
If you've decided to accept a world
where Okabe Rintarou doesn't exist, there's no point in me remaining.
I'll ask you one last time.
Aren't you going to change your mind?
There's no record of Okabe Rintarou on this world line from this point now on.
In other words, once I go back, you'll never see him again.
Is that still what you want?
Okabe told me not to change the past, no matter what happens.
I agree with him. The risks are too—
That's not my question! What does your heart tell you!?
I won't... change... my mind.
So that's how it's going to be...
You know, in the future, you'll build the time machine.
What do you mean?
Makise Kurisu develops the time machine.
But she won't authorize its use, and will ask my father to seal it off,
saying that it's the will of Okabe Rintarou.
In other words, you'll keep contradicting yourself.
You'll find a way to return to the past to help and see him,
and even build the time machine,
but you'll give up in the end because you can't be honest with yourself.
You'll do this over and over again.
That's why you—
I thought that the you of the past might be more true to yourself.
But you're still the same stubborn girl.
How can you—
It's the truth.
I am a scientist!
My actions are based on my theories and my beliefs.
I can't be swayed by emotion—
You always pretend to be cool-headed like that!
You really get on my nerves!
It's the same for me!
Okabe Rintarou is no more...
but the world keeps on going.
It keeps on going as if nothing ever happened.
But you'll build the time machine.
What's more important to you?
Your pride and ethical code as a scientist?
Is that enough for you?
Is there a reason for you to live in this world?
This is the time machine?
Let's go.
Is it really possible?
The future you said it was.
If you change the past, the world line will shift.
That's why you won't change any of the events that occurred,
but only alter Okabe Rintarou's memory.
His memory...
Okabe Rintarou is unable to recognize the Steins Gate
world line as the real world.
So you only need to make him recognize that this world line
is distinctly different from the others.
That's why I have to alter his memory?
Yes.
Anchor a powerful memory that isn't present in any other world line.
Then the present world line will be imprinted on his brain as something distinctly different
from the others, and he will be freed from his Reading Steiner overload.
That does sound correct in theory. True to my reputation.
But you didn't even try to go to the past.
Sit down over there.
That was my scientist's conscience. You should be praising me.
Narcissist...
How rude! It's not like that, I'm just... a scientist.
You're just like her. Well, you're the same person after all.
Come on, let's go. To what year?
You don't know?
You should know better than me
when the best time to plant a powerful memory in Okabe Rintarou's brain would be.
2005.
Based on what?
Something Mayuri told me.
Powerful memories are generated by powerful events.
Gotcha. I'll trust you.
Let's go! The force is a bit strong, so be prepared!
Now it's up to you. You have no cell phone, so to get in touch—
Wait! What am I supposed to do?
I already told you the objective, but I don't know
how to plant a powerful memory in Okabe Rintarou's head.
You said you would know what to do.
The future me did?
Yes.
I found Mayuri's address, but there was no way
to obtain Okabe's after he had disappeared from this world line.
Shiina
It should be near this house, but...
If I find him, then what?
How do I talk to him? What do I do?
If I fail...
A change in the past will always affect something else.
It will never change in a way that's convenient for you.
Okabe?
Okabe!
Okabe! Okabe!
Wait! I need to talk to you!
Don't worry. The world will return to normal.
Right... Okabe is never ever going to die there!
It's all right. There's no need to worry about it!
But I keep wondering... If I return to the past again,
will Okabe get hit by a car again?
Or perhaps an even more terrifying change will occur.
If I interfere, something like that could easily happen...
But the Okabe Rintarou of that time won't die anyway.
Don't you understand, Amane?
The fact that Okabe absolutely won't die
also means that I absolutely won't be able to help him!
But the future you—
Okabe had to endure this feeling of powerlessness
all by himself, all this time!
I couldn't possibly...
Let's see, this is...
Oh, Kurisu!
Tutturu~
Hello.
Say, is this "furniture" or "audio"?
Are you throwing that away?
Yeah. Daru told me
to just stick the disposal ticket on it.
I see.
It's kind of sad, isn't it?
Yes.
But that's how it is.
Listen, Kurisu.
Do you know about... "Okarin"?
You see, when I'm here, sometimes that word just pops into my head
while I'm tidying up or making costumes,
or even eating...
I don't...
Kurisu?
Makise!
Urushibara...
You're training hard.
Yes. I do 100 swings a day to
unleash Samidare's true power.
Interesting name. Did you choose it?
Yes...
No, it wasn't—
This katana...
I think someone gave it to me.
Stop it!
It's a virus, nyan~!
It feels so good to get beaten up by you, Faris!
8-0
It's so one-sided.
Kurisu showed up!
What are you doing?
We were doing a Rai-Net battle at MayQueen when
Faris suddenly said she wanted to play against the head of the lab!
She summoned me on my way back from a part-time job interview!
An interview?
Yup.
I want to try to at least be able to pay the lab's rent.
It's better if the lab exists, don't you think?
Hashida...
But something's different, nyan~.
The head of the lab used to play...
Better?
No. He sucked, nyan~. Catastrophically.
But I think he was much livelier, nyan~!
Like a real battle?
No, nyan~! But like...
Daru-nyan, strike a pose, nyan~!
Like this?
No, nyan~!
I think I understand...
There should be one more...
One more?
But he's not here...
Déjà vu!
As I suspected, it's not a delusion your brain is showing you.
Déjà vu is a manifestation of Reading Steiner!
They're memories of another world line...
I exist on countless world lines.
The convergence of those lines and all those memories coming together
makes me who I am now.
A one and only me.
Your mightily annoying self won't disappear from anyone's heart.
Even when you think you've been forgotten, our memories of you
will always remain somewhere...
I tried to give up.
I tried to forget so many times.
I thought it'd be impossible, even with the time machine.
But I feel like everyone is telling me not to forget!
I...
Ku-nyan? What's wrong, nyan~?
I am...
Hououin Kyouma!
My goal is to reform this world's ruling structure!
To accomplish this, the Future Gadget Lab
must develop an invention that will plunge the world into chaos!
Did the heat make you go nuts?
But I've seen this before, nyan~.
Stop it...
Be silent, Supah Hakah!
I am a mad scientist!
That's the scenario again? Wait.
What am I saying?
Don't remember!
Mayuri! The intellectual beverage of the chosen ones!
Good evening... Oh?
Rukako! Don't neglect your practice swings!
Y-Yes, sir!
The hidden power of the demon sword Samidare can only be unlocked
through sheer discipline!
Yes, sir!
It's useless... I can't help him...
Here you go, Kurisu. Your Dr Pepper.
But you know, Kurisu, you aren't Hououin Kyouma.
Hououin Kyouma is...
Okabe Rintarou...
Oka... rin?
Okarin? Sounds familiar. But my mind is still fuzzy.
Okarin? Do you mean Kyouma, nyan~?
...Okabe?
Oka... Kyouma!
Okarin... Okarin...
I don't know who that is,
but when I say his name, I feel warm inside.
I wonder why.
Everyone is watching something other than themselves,
something important to them,
just like you did when you were observing us.
Even if you're not in this world...
Even if there's no trace of you here...
People's feelings will still cross world lines.
But...
Soon, Okabe will pass by, just like before.
I've made it this far, but I don't know what to do.
How can I save him?
Even if our feelings cross world lines, the events will still revert back!
Then what can I do?
Whatever I do will be useless!
Don't you have an umbrella?
You're still wet! No umbrella?
I don't know anything about Okabe.
All I have are fragments.
Slight memories from this world line
and the ones from other world lines, called déjà vu.
The past me would have never considered changing the past or building a time machine
because there was nothing I wanted to protect that badly.
But I finally found something...
I still haven't told him anything about how I feel...
Every time I saw him, I always acted stubborn
and quarreled with him.
I couldn't tell him what I really wanted to say.
Since I was little, I've always tried to do everything on my own
by building walls around me
and refusing any help.
An unpleasant child...
No wonder my father didn't like me.
But the truth is, I wanted someone to call out to me.
I wanted someone to say,
even if I was the only one there, "I'm here watching."
Are you lost?
Me too.
A girl I've known since I was little is really depressed...
I don't know what to say to her...
I wonder if I'm just useless...
Have you heard of... Hououin Kyouma?
Hououin?
He's a scientist. But not just any scientist.
He's a mad scientist and a first-rate one at that.
He talked and behaved crazily,
and everyone always made a fool of him.
Nobody believed what he said, in his research, or in his discoveries.
But you know, what he uncovered was something that only he
could see.
He realized that it could hurt and cause pain
and even destroy the world at times.
So he tried with all his might to protect everyone.
He continued to fight to save the world
and managed to protect all of the people dear to him.
But nobody ever knew about it.
He went on being a mad scientist the entire time,
and everybody kept on making a fool of him.
That's a sad story.
Really? I think it's a wonderful story.
Go now.
I'm sure someone is waiting for you.
Mayuri!
Okarin?
I'm not letting them take you!
You're my hostage, Mayuri!
I'm going to use you for human experimentation!
Are you ready? I will now give an overview of Operation Norn!
What are you gawking at? Pervert!
You...
What are you doing here?
I didn't come to you. You're trying to come back
from this world to the Steins Gate world line.
Remember the times you wandered through the world lines?
I was always with you.
Mayuri, Hashida, Faris,
Urushibara, Kiryuu, and Amane
haven't forgotten you.
You were so arrogant to think that you were holding up the world by yourself!
Don't forget.
No matter what world line you're on, you'll never be alone.
I'll find you, wherever you are!
I will continue to observe you
just as you kept on observing me.
If that's the Steins Gate's choice.
Well, Cristina, care to return it to me?
...My first kiss.
Never.
Itsuka bokura ga mirai furikaeru toki ni wa
Someday in the future, we will look back
Load Region of Deja Vu
itsumo kono basho de kimi ga waratte
To see you smiling, always here
TUTTURUTUTTURUTUTTURUTUTTURUTUTTURUTUTTURU
zankoku ni sugiyuku toki no naka de sagashimotome te i ta mono
What I was searching for in the cruelly fast flow of time
surechigau sekai ni tojikome rare ta me ni mie nu hikari
An invisible light, trapped between worlds passing by one another
tokubetsu na hodo aisuru mono he uchiakerare zu ni i ta
I never opened my heart to the one I love - the one special to me
sugoshi ta hibi no hitotsu hitotsu ga tomadoi o piriodo ni kaeru
The passage of time puts an end to all my doubts
itsuka bokura ga mirai furikaeru toki ni wa
Someday in the future, we will look back
itsumo kono basho de kimi ga waratte
To see you smiling, always here
kasaneatta minna no omoi ga sekai sen o tsukuru
Our thoughts and feelings will combine to form a new world line
donna ame ni mo make nu shinjiaeru kimochi
With a belief in one another that no rain can defeat
kono sora no kansoku sha kono sora wa ashita no shoumei
The Observer of the sky - the sky that proves we have a future
ano hi bokura ha deai taisetsu na nani ka o
On the day we met I found something important
itsumo kono basho de sagashi te i ta ne
I'd been searching for a long time, and it was always here
nanigenaku sugiyuku jikan no sono imi o shitteru
I know the importance of time passing uneventfully
tatoe donnani ni nin hanare te shimatte mo
No matter the distance between us
kono sora no kansoku sha kono sora wa ashita no shoumei
The Observer of the sky - the sky that proves we have a future